I've been to the rainforest
我曾去过雨林
To the ocean
海洋
To the snow mountains
和雪山
met situations I least expected
也遇到了最出乎预料的情况
I was looking for more creative ways
我在寻找更有创意的方法
to explore the world
来探索这个世界
That's when i thought
那时我就想
Let's give discovery a call
来联络探索频道试试看
I want to leave the city life behind
我想抛开城市生活
Go deep into nature
深入大自然
in search of something untamed
寻找那份狂野
Pure and mysterious
纯洁而神秘
I thought i was leaving the concrete jungle behind
我以为我要远离了水泥丛林
But towering trees here
但这里的参天大树
remind me of tall buildings
却让我想起高楼大厦
and hum in the air of traffic
以及不绝于耳的车流声
They say valleys and peaks
他们说山谷和山峰
mirror life's ups and downs
反映了生活的起起伏伏
I wonder
我想知道
Is that why mountains are sacred
这就是为什么山是神圣的吗？
I hope this journey provides space for reflection and growth
我希望这次旅行能提供反思和成长的空间
Every peak
Whether in the career or on the mountain
每一座高峰
无论是在事业上还是在山上
Comes with its own challenges
都有自己的挑战
We are in Gansu Ka，Qinghai
我们在青海的岗什卡
I will be climbing my first 5000-meter peak
我将攀登我的第一个5000米高峰
Then snowboard my way back down
然后滑着滑雪板下山